<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://chulianyuang.github.io</id>
    <title>welcome to my world • Posts by &#34;英语角&#34; tag</title>
    <link href="https://chulianyuang.github.io" />
    <updated>2023-02-28T14:15:04.000Z</updated>
    <category term="C语言函数复习" />
    <category term="三省吾身" />
    <category term="小白学C语言" />
    <category term="C语言大一上学期期末复习" />
    <category term="细解" />
    <category term="习题汇总" />
    <category term="题库" />
    <category term="maven工程+Mybatis+IDEA" />
    <category term="Front-end project" />
    <category term="网页设计" />
    <category term="巧思" />
    <category term="细化操作" />
    <category term="中二病" />
    <category term="Java项目" />
    <category term="练习题" />
    <category term="动态规划" />
    <category term="历史早读" />
    <category term="大学计划1" />
    <category term="鸡汤" />
    <category term="C语言探索" />
    <category term="性理解" />
    <category term="项目一-学生管理系统" />
    <category term="慢节奏的生活" />
    <category term="C语言指针复习" />
    <category term="小测" />
    <category term="期末复习" />
    <category term="习题答案" />
    <category term="《Me for you》翻译" />
    <category term="栈和队列" />
    <category term="日常小作" />
    <category term="环境保护" />
    <category term="矩阵与求解" />
    <category term="慢慢就爱上的科目" />
    <category term="知识点总结" />
    <category term="C语言复习" />
    <category term="从年头红到年尾" />
    <category term="课前五分钟" />
    <category term="全国英语四级考试" />
    <category term="英语角" />
    <category term="蓝桥杯" />
    <category term="课前演讲" />
    <category term="概念介绍" />
    <category term="C语言实验报告" />
    <category term="实训报告" />
    <category term="关于创业的一条路" />
    <category term="知识总结" />
    <category term="Java" />
    <category term="面试" />
    <entry>
        <id>https://chulianyuang.github.io/2023/02/28/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E8%A7%92/</id>
        <title>制药公司可以合法开始销售可卡因、海洛因和摇头丸</title>
        <link rel="alternate" href="https://chulianyuang.github.io/2023/02/28/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E8%A7%92/"/>
        <content type="html">&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;An anonymous reader quotes a report from Motherboard:&lt;em&gt;At least two companies in British Columbia, Canada, say they’ve received exemptions from the federal government &lt;span class=&#34;exturl&#34; data-url=&#34;aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cudmljZS5jb20vZW4vYXJ0aWNsZS85M2s5NTcvY2FuYWRhLWJjLWNvY2FpbmUtc2FsZQ==&#34;&gt;allowing them to produce and distribute cocaine, heroin, MDMA, or magic mushrooms&lt;/span&gt;. But it’s not clear under what circumstances the companies will be able to sell the drugs, and B.C. Premier David Eby said he was “astonished” to hear the announcement. On Thursday, Sunshine Earth Labs, a psychedelics manufacturer &lt;span class=&#34;exturl&#34; data-url=&#34;aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cubmV3c3dpcmUuY2EvbmV3cy1yZWxlYXNlcy9zdW5zaGluZS1lYXJ0aC1sYWJzLWx0ZC1wcm92aWRlcy1jb3Jwb3JhdGUtdXBkYXRlLTg0OTEzMjE1Ny5odG1s&#34;&gt;announced&lt;/span&gt; that Health Canada, a federal government agency, is allowing the company to legally produce and distribute the coca leaf and cocaine; MDMA; opium; morphine, heroin and psilocybin, the active ingredient in shrooms. The company said it plans to “bring a safer supply of drugs to the global market.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meanwhile, cannabis extractions company Adastra &lt;span class=&#34;exturl&#34; data-url=&#34;aHR0cHM6Ly9hZGFzdHJhaG9sZGluZ3MuY2EvYWRhc3RyYS1sYWJzLXJlY2VpdmVzLWhlYWx0aC1jYW5hZGEtYXBwcm92YWwtZm9yLXRoZS1hbWVuZG1lbnQtdG8taW5jbHVkZS1jb2NhaW5lLXVuZGVyLWl0cy1jb250cm9sbGVkLXN1YnN0YW5jZXMtZGVhbGVycy1saWNlbnNlLw==&#34;&gt;announced&lt;/span&gt; it’s now legally allowed to both produce and distribute psilocybin and cocaine. In a statement to VICE News, Health Canada said Adastra is licensed to produce the drugs for scientific and medical purposes but cannot sell products to the general public. “They are only permitted for sale to other licence holders who have cocaine listed on their licence, pharmacists, practitioners, hospitals, or the holder of a section 56(1) exemption for research purposes,” the agency said.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Both companies claim they received amendments under Health Canada’s Dealer’s Licenses, which grant manufacturers, doctors, and researchers exemptions to the Controlled Drugs and Substances Act, allowing them to legally possess and make banned drugs. In a news conference, Eby said the licenses were granted without consultation from the province. “It is not part of our provincial plan,” he said, noting that he would be following up with Health Canada about the announcements. Adastra said it’s license allows it to &amp;quot;interact with up to 250 grams of cocaine and to import coca leaves to manufacture and synthesize the substance.&amp;quot;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Posted by &lt;span class=&#34;exturl&#34; data-url=&#34;aHR0cHM6Ly90d2l0dGVyLmNvbS9CZWF1SEQ=&#34;&gt;BeauHD&lt;/span&gt; on Friday March 03, 2023 @10:30PM from the how-about-that dept&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
        <category term="英语角" />
        <updated>2023-02-28T14:15:04.000Z</updated>
    </entry>
</feed>
