<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>welcome to my world • Posts by &#34;大学进阶英语&#34; category</title>
        <link>http://example.com</link>
        <description></description>
        <language>zh-CN</language>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 01:16:38 +0800</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 01:16:38 +0800</lastBuildDate>
        <category>三省吾身</category>
        <category>C语言函数复习</category>
        <category>小白学C语言</category>
        <category>细解</category>
        <category>巧思</category>
        <category>细化操作</category>
        <category>C语言大一上学期期末复习</category>
        <category>中二病</category>
        <category>练习题</category>
        <category>动态规划</category>
        <category>大学计划1</category>
        <category>鸡汤</category>
        <category>C语言探索</category>
        <category>慢节奏的生活</category>
        <category>历史早读</category>
        <category>性理解</category>
        <category>C语言指针复习</category>
        <category>习题答案</category>
        <category>栈和队列</category>
        <category>日常小作</category>
        <category>矩阵与求解</category>
        <category>环境保护</category>
        <category>慢慢就爱上的科目</category>
        <category>知识点总结</category>
        <category>C语言复习</category>
        <category>从年头红到年尾</category>
        <category>课前五分钟</category>
        <category>全国英语四级考试</category>
        <category>英语角</category>
        <category>课前演讲</category>
        <category>C语言实验报告</category>
        <category>关于创业的一条路</category>
        <category>知识总结</category>
        <category>期末复习</category>
        <category>软件设计师考核</category>
        <category>题库</category>
        <category>Java入门</category>
        <category>网页设计</category>
        <category>《Me for you》翻译</category>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">http://example.com/2023/08/06/%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E8%A7%84%E5%88%92/</guid>
            <title>暑假规划</title>
            <link>http://example.com/2023/08/06/%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E8%A7%84%E5%88%92/</link>
            <category>《Me for you》翻译</category>
            <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 01:16:38 +0800</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;h1 id=&#34;me-for-you&#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;markdownIt-Anchor&#34; href=&#34;#me-for-you&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt; ME FOR YOU&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;暑假还有一个月就结束了，接下来的我就是大二的老牛了，我总感觉大一好像并没有学到什么，比赛也没有怎么参加，我知道自身的情况，但我可以保证我大一确实没有荒废时间，不得不说，还是比较喜欢高中被老师撵着前行的日子，进入大学后基本上就是自学了，老师不怎么管你，但是自学真的好乱啊，我是准备参加大三的秋招的，但以我现在的实力，我真的不知到应该怎么写才能被企业招聘。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最近我逛招聘网站发现大型的 IT 公司贴出来的人才需求上写着四六级英语优先，现在大家这么卷，优先在这个时代就是基础要求的意思，所以我准备学英语啦，先把四六级考试证书拿下再说，我本来是想大一去考的，但我实力差了点，上学期考试不给力，没有考到 A 班，所以连参加考试的资格都没有。但大二就是我们 B 班去考试了，我争取一次过，所以从今天开始，我明天都会自己试着去翻译一章英语名著。不过现在得先睡觉，hh。&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">http://example.com/2023/05/23/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E6%BC%94%E8%AE%B22/</guid>
            <title>英语演讲</title>
            <link>http://example.com/2023/05/23/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E6%BC%94%E8%AE%B22/</link>
            <category>课前五分钟</category>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 16:14:51 +0800</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;h1 id=&#34;AI创作歌曲火出圈，引发音乐行业恐慌&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#AI创作歌曲火出圈，引发音乐行业恐慌&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;AI创作歌曲火出圈，引发音乐行业恐慌&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;AI创作歌曲火出圈，引发音乐行业恐慌&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img data-src=&#34;https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/chulianyuang/imap/202305231652128.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;OIP-C&#34; style=&#34;zoom:;&#34; /&gt;&lt;img data-src=&#34;https://ts1.cn.mm.bing.net/th/id/R-C.d2471a686aaae91cc575a242d85a4a30?rik=SIAdrmFbgMT0ag&amp;riu=http%3a%2f%2fwww.tmtage.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2017%2f12%2f20171213ai.jpg&amp;ehk=a03Ri%2bcpPR4gS%2bu2m%2fR4IUv0gHSJ9JNMD76TNLQKjGo%3d&amp;risl=&amp;pid=ImgRaw&amp;r=0&#34; alt=&#34;AI创作物的法律保护不容忽视-蓝时代&#34;  /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The viral song “Heart on My Sleeve,” released last week by TikTok user Ghostwriter977  but made popular because of its purported use of Al-generated vocals mimicking superstars Drake and The Weeknd, has caused quite a stir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img data-src=&#34;https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/chulianyuang/imap/202305231655848.png&#34; alt=&#34;image-20230523165547639&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It comes on the heels of an Al-generated Rihanna singing”Cuff lt” and an Al Kendrick Lamar rapping Ye’s “Off the Grid”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each release is followed by a great deal of conversation, with some listeners proclaiming a new frontier in music technology and others astonished by the seemingly uncanny likeness to the source material.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The song sparked a panic within the music industry in a way none of the previous Al-generated tracks did, perhaps because of its popularity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It received more than 15 million views on TikTok, 600,000 streams on Spotify and 275,000 views on YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The BBC estimated the song earned at least $1.888 from Spotify alone; Billboard&lt;br&gt;estimated the song may have earned $9,400 globally across all platforms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason those numbers aren’t higher is “Heart on My Sleeve” has since been removed from all digital service providers following a complaint by Universal Music Group, who released a statement condemning “infringing content created with generative Al.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But attempting to crack down on Al-generated music may pose a unique challenge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The legal landscape for Al work remains unclear the tools to create it are widely accessible and social media makes it easier than ever to distribute it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although the entertainment industry has seen these issues coming, regulations are lagging behind the rapid pace of Al development.&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">http://example.com/2023/03/03/%E7%8E%AF%E5%A2%83%E4%BF%9D%E6%8A%A4%E5%B0%8F%E4%BD%9C/</guid>
            <title>环境保护小作</title>
            <link>http://example.com/2023/03/03/%E7%8E%AF%E5%A2%83%E4%BF%9D%E6%8A%A4%E5%B0%8F%E4%BD%9C/</link>
            <category>环境保护</category>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:47:19 +0800</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In high school, I was impressed by a word in a magazine, “The earth does not need humans, but humans cannot do without the earth, at least for now.” &amp;quot;In my opinion,the earth is sick today, and protecting the environment and recycling is a very important and urgent thing. Mother Earth is tolerance that she rarely gets angry at us for doing something that hurts it, but we can’t take this love for granted. It is time for us to make environment-friendly choices, such as sorting garbage into recyclable groups, saving water and electricity, using less plastic bags, plant more trees, and take more public transportation. I believe that with our efforts, the blue sky will definitely be bluer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">http://example.com/2023/02/28/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E8%A7%92/</guid>
            <title>制药公司可以合法开始销售可卡因、海洛因和摇头丸</title>
            <link>http://example.com/2023/02/28/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E8%A7%92/</link>
            <category>英语角</category>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 22:15:04 +0800</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;An anonymous reader quotes a report from Motherboard:&lt;em&gt;At least two companies in British Columbia, Canada, say they’ve received exemptions from the federal government &lt;span class=&#34;exturl&#34; data-url=&#34;aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cudmljZS5jb20vZW4vYXJ0aWNsZS85M2s5NTcvY2FuYWRhLWJjLWNvY2FpbmUtc2FsZQ==&#34;&gt;allowing them to produce and distribute cocaine, heroin, MDMA, or magic mushrooms&lt;/span&gt;. But it’s not clear under what circumstances the companies will be able to sell the drugs, and B.C. Premier David Eby said he was “astonished” to hear the announcement. On Thursday, Sunshine Earth Labs, a psychedelics manufacturer &lt;span class=&#34;exturl&#34; data-url=&#34;aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cubmV3c3dpcmUuY2EvbmV3cy1yZWxlYXNlcy9zdW5zaGluZS1lYXJ0aC1sYWJzLWx0ZC1wcm92aWRlcy1jb3Jwb3JhdGUtdXBkYXRlLTg0OTEzMjE1Ny5odG1s&#34;&gt;announced&lt;/span&gt; that Health Canada, a federal government agency, is allowing the company to legally produce and distribute the coca leaf and cocaine; MDMA; opium; morphine, heroin and psilocybin, the active ingredient in shrooms. The company said it plans to “bring a safer supply of drugs to the global market.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meanwhile, cannabis extractions company Adastra &lt;span class=&#34;exturl&#34; data-url=&#34;aHR0cHM6Ly9hZGFzdHJhaG9sZGluZ3MuY2EvYWRhc3RyYS1sYWJzLXJlY2VpdmVzLWhlYWx0aC1jYW5hZGEtYXBwcm92YWwtZm9yLXRoZS1hbWVuZG1lbnQtdG8taW5jbHVkZS1jb2NhaW5lLXVuZGVyLWl0cy1jb250cm9sbGVkLXN1YnN0YW5jZXMtZGVhbGVycy1saWNlbnNlLw==&#34;&gt;announced&lt;/span&gt; it’s now legally allowed to both produce and distribute psilocybin and cocaine. In a statement to VICE News, Health Canada said Adastra is licensed to produce the drugs for scientific and medical purposes but cannot sell products to the general public. “They are only permitted for sale to other licence holders who have cocaine listed on their licence, pharmacists, practitioners, hospitals, or the holder of a section 56(1) exemption for research purposes,” the agency said.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Both companies claim they received amendments under Health Canada’s Dealer’s Licenses, which grant manufacturers, doctors, and researchers exemptions to the Controlled Drugs and Substances Act, allowing them to legally possess and make banned drugs. In a news conference, Eby said the licenses were granted without consultation from the province. “It is not part of our provincial plan,” he said, noting that he would be following up with Health Canada about the announcements. Adastra said it’s license allows it to &amp;quot;interact with up to 250 grams of cocaine and to import coca leaves to manufacture and synthesize the substance.&amp;quot;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Posted by &lt;span class=&#34;exturl&#34; data-url=&#34;aHR0cHM6Ly90d2l0dGVyLmNvbS9CZWF1SEQ=&#34;&gt;BeauHD&lt;/span&gt; on Friday March 03, 2023 @10:30PM from the how-about-that dept&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">http://example.com/2023/02/27/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%A4%8D%E4%B9%A0/</guid>
            <title>英语复习</title>
            <link>http://example.com/2023/02/27/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%A4%8D%E4%B9%A0/</link>
            <category>全国英语四级考试</category>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 21:36:44 +0800</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;h1 id=&#34;课文再复习&#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;markdownIt-Anchor&#34; href=&#34;#课文再复习&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt; 课文再复习&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;living-off-the-grid-how-a-family-of-city-dwellers-discovered-the-simple-life&#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;markdownIt-Anchor&#34; href=&#34;#living-off-the-grid-how-a-family-of-city-dwellers-discovered-the-simple-life&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt; Living off the grid :How a Family of City-Dwellers Discovered the Simple Life&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After living in the 24-hour city of Las Vegas , Nevada for nearly ten years,my family and I decided to slow things down. My daughter wanted a horse .My husband wanted property .My son wanted a dirt bike. I wanted our family to be more self-sufficient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;None of us felt that this could be accomplished where we were living and we all agreed that a move to the country would be great for everyone .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before long we set about looking for a home in Yucca , Arizona , a very small town of less than 1000 people . It was while I scanning listings from our real estate agent that I first learned of it . There was a home for sale there on 40 acres . When I called to inquire about the property,I was informed that there was no electricity available in the area . What ? No electricity ? I almost dismissed the idea immediately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The property was off the grid . It was not connected whatsoever to any utilities -power , water or sewer . Power was supplied by a wind turbine and solar panels . Water had to hauled in and stored in two tanks located on the property. Forty acres would give us plenty of room for all of our animals and give my husband and sun space to ride their ATVS . Beside , what better thing is there to become more self-sustainable ? After giving it some thought , we decided to put in an offer and move in on Thanksgiving Day.&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">http://example.com/2022/12/10/%E6%A2%A6%E6%83%B3%E4%B8%AD%E7%9A%84%E5%B7%A5%E4%BD%9C/</guid>
            <title>梦想中的工作</title>
            <link>http://example.com/2022/12/10/%E6%A2%A6%E6%83%B3%E4%B8%AD%E7%9A%84%E5%B7%A5%E4%BD%9C/</link>
            <category>日常小作</category>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 23:06:01 +0800</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;h1 id=&#34;my-dream-job&#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;markdownIt-Anchor&#34; href=&#34;#my-dream-job&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt; My dream job&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In fact, my dream job should be to have no job and I can take my partner and my family to travel around the world every day enjoying the beauty of nature and eating all kinds of food. But I know this is unrealistic. Therefore, my dream job become creating an Internet company. Only when I have enough strength can I play at will. I thing dream is a little divorced from reality and can not leave reality. It feels just like science fiction. As a boy, I must have ambition. I want to build an Internet company stronger than Google  which is my dream job. I know it’s almost impossible, but maybe!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My company job in the Internet company is to maintain the normal operation of the virtual world. In my opinion, people in the future will completely will abandon mobile phones to play games. The mobile phone will return to its original function ,which is communication. People will swim in the virtual world through the equipment provided by our company, and 100% simulate the five senses of players. The main profit of our company will be the percentage of players trading in the virtual world.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;However, if I want to create an Internet company, I must have excellent computer technology. Not only do I need to learn the knowledge of my major, but I also need to master the knowledge of other computer majors. There is also equity knowledge, management knowledge and legal knowledge, so it is difficult to start a business. Another thing is that starting a business can’t do without capital. I don’t want to rely on my family more. So after graduation, I should work in a large Internet company for three or four years to complete my capital accumulation. This will also let me know how other companies operate and learn from experience. After all, starting a business is not a joke, and it is good to increase the success rate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;In terms of how to work hard in college, I don’t really have a plan. But there are also some ideas. First of all, I need to find partners who share the same interests with me in some neighborhoods, so that I will not deviate from the direction when I live with them. After all, it’s not easy not to forget your original intention. What’s more, we need to learn online faster than the teachers teach, so that we can have more opportunities to participate in the competition than the students of the same class. Don’t put the opportunity in front of me at that time. I really didn’t seize it because I didn’t learn enough knowledge.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;我梦想中的工作&#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;markdownIt-Anchor&#34; href=&#34;#我梦想中的工作&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt; 我梦想中的工作&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;其实在我看来我梦想中的工作应该是没有工作，每天带着我的伴侣和我的家人去世界各地游玩，领略自然的美和吃遍各地美食，但我知道这不现实。因此，我梦想中的工作就变成了开一家互联网公司，只有我有足够实力的时候我才能随心所欲的去玩。这里说的是梦想，也就是说有点脱离现实的，又不能离开现实，感觉跟科幻小说一样。那我作为一个男生不妨野心大点，我要创建一家比谷歌还要强的互联网公司。我知道这几乎不可能，但也许呢！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我的互联网公司主要职务是维护虚拟世界的正常运行。在我看来，未来的人们将彻底抛弃手机玩游戏。手机将回归它原本的功能，也就是只有通讯功能。人们将通过我公司提供的设备身临其境的在虚拟世界中畅游，百分百的模拟玩家的五感。我公司的主要盈利将是玩家在虚拟世界中交易的抽成。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;不过想要创建互联网公司，作为未来老板的我必须具备高超的电脑技术。不单是我这个专业的知识要学，其它计算机专业的知识我也要掌握。还有就是股权知识，管理知识，法律知识也要略懂，所以创业很难。还有就是创业离不开资金，我不想过多依靠家里，所以毕业后我应该会去大的互联网公司工作三四年完成我的资本积累，这样也可以让我熟悉一些别人的公司是怎么运作的，学习经验，毕竟创业可不是儿戏，能增加一丝成功率都是好的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;要说在大学应该如何为之努力的话，我其实还不是很有计划。但也有想法，首先我要找到与我在一些邻域志同道合的伙伴，与之共处才不会让自己偏离了方向。毕竟不忘初心谈何容易。还有的就是要在网上学习的比老师教的要快，这样才能比同届的同学多一些参加比赛实践的机会。别到时候机会摆在我面前，我确因为知识没有学习到位没有抓住它。&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">http://example.com/2022/12/02/%E5%A4%A7%E5%AD%A6%E8%BF%9B%E9%98%B6%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD/</guid>
            <title>一路向前</title>
            <link>http://example.com/2022/12/02/%E5%A4%A7%E5%AD%A6%E8%BF%9B%E9%98%B6%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD/</link>
            <category>鸡汤</category>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 18:16:39 +0800</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;h1 id=&#34;2022-12-2&#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;markdownIt-Anchor&#34; href=&#34;#2022-12-2&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt; 2022 12 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-higher-i-got-the-more-amazed-i-was-by-the-view&#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;markdownIt-Anchor&#34; href=&#34;#the-higher-i-got-the-more-amazed-i-was-by-the-view&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt; The higher I got ,the more amazed I was by the view&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;我爬得越高，眼前的风景便愈发迷人&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">http://example.com/2022/12/02/%E8%AF%BE%E5%89%8D%E4%BA%94%E5%88%86%E9%92%9F%E4%B8%AD%E8%8B%B1%E5%8F%8C%E7%89%88/</guid>
            <title>课前五分钟中英双版</title>
            <link>http://example.com/2022/12/02/%E8%AF%BE%E5%89%8D%E4%BA%94%E5%88%86%E9%92%9F%E4%B8%AD%E8%8B%B1%E5%8F%8C%E7%89%88/</link>
            <category>课前演讲</category>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 13:24:04 +0800</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;h1 id=&#34;the-charm-of-cantonese&#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;markdownIt-Anchor&#34; href=&#34;#the-charm-of-cantonese&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt; The charm of Cantonese&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compared to Mandarin, Cantonese has more variability in tone. From a language point of view alone, such a language will make a good impression, so it is more layered into the song. Mainlanders prefer Cantonese songs because the language has a unique charm, and it will be more distinctive when added to the melody. Even if you can’t understand the meaning of the lyrics, you still cannot help  humming along . Cantonese is loved by many audiences and fans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cantonese itself has a retro flavor. The reason why there is a retro taste is because the elements of ancient Chinese are still retained in the process of development. In order to adapt to the development of the times,many languages are becoming easier and simpler  and some older words will be omitted or abandoned in the process, so that the language becomes more understandable. However, there are still some older words and pronunciations in Cantonese, which will add a historical atmosphere and cultural heritage to the language. Due to the existence of ancient Chinese elements, this language also has a more simple and elegant atmosphere, and adding melody and rhythm to Cantonese songs is more flavorful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Daily expressions&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你好&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你好&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你叫什么名字？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你叫咩啊？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;谢谢！&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;唔该！多谢嗮！&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;不好意思打扰你一下&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;唔好意思阻你一阵&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;在哪里呀？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;喺边度呀？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你在干什么？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你喺度做乜？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你吃饭了没？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你食咗饭未？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I just say that, you should not be able to have a deep feeling about the language of Cantonese. Next, I will share with you a popular Cantonese song. I wish that we can appreciate the unique beauty of Cantonese while listening, so as to end this speech. In my opinion,The success of a speech depends on whether it can resonate with the audience, and I hope that this talk of mine will give you something out of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for listening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[&lt;span class=&#34;exturl&#34; data-url=&#34;aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cua3Vnb3UuY29tL3NvbmcvZ2dqcG84MS5odG1sI2hhc2g9RTg0OTQ3NDAyQTVFMDk1MkZBMDY3NTY2QzEwMjY0Q0ImYW1wO2FsYnVtX2lkPTg1NDM0NjE=&#34;&gt;https://www.kugou.com/song/ggjpo81.html#hash=E84947402A5E0952FA067566C10264CB&amp;amp;album_id=8543461&lt;/span&gt;]:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jcool：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;有个女仔令我思想变得大个&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;当初&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我幼稚行为对你犯下大错&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;你话我唔识谂 用钱买无用饰品&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;你慢慢心淡觉得我对感情唔认真&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;要知道男人系天生嘅小朋友&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;小朋友弱点会忽略另一半感受&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;要改正好简单我只系欠调教&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;经历得多反而可以令到爱意浓厚&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vai：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;志明嘅世界永远好动带着可爱&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;佢冇时间迷茫 爱情错过却唔可再&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;从开始走到结尾哪个不会变大个&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但春娇想要那个你又有谁可以劝阻&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;等待 UFO 纵有变数&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最普通嘅佢哋世上遍布&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爱漫春天散落每个季节嘅消耗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;看着花瓣跌落过程撑得过衰老&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;欧阳：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;重新出发吗 huh 更渴望未来&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;以往这少年懂爱吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;仿佛不够&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;成长会进化吗 也信念自由&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我爱这少年讽刺吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这花开吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;留：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我爱你 你是唱将我做配合&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但你予我这过程细致给我培训&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;情与爱 太过复杂 我要太多喘息&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但你爱我嘅以后不会太过忐忑&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;当拥有嘅时候 又接近放手&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;循环播放剧情有多少个然后&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;如果系现实我会选择打破现实&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;喺你嘅世界里面我会选择慢慢渐入&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vai：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;志明嘅世界永远好动带着可爱&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;佢冇时间迷茫 爱情错过却唔可再&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;从开始走到结尾哪个不会变大个&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但春娇想要那个你又有谁可以劝阻&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;等待 UFO 纵有变数&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最普通嘅佢哋世上遍布&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爱漫春天散落每个季节嘅消耗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;看着花瓣跌落过程撑得过衰老&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;欧阳：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;重新出发吗 huh 更渴望未来&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;以往这少年懂爱吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;仿佛不够&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;成长会进化吗 也信念自由&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我爱这少年讽刺吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这花开吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Garyu：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;破碎婚姻里出身逼出佢嘅硬净&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;佢再牺牲佢嘅率真改变佢嘅硬颈&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;戴眼镜嘅佢明白波珠解决唔到逃避&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;要长大要负责任缩短两个人嘅距离&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;美梦里学会感嘅&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;你亦放肆你的爱&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;用力转载 越过比赛&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;为我掩盖 都因为爱&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;欧阳：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;重新出发吗 huh 更渴望未来&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;以往这少年懂爱吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;仿佛不够&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;成长会进化吗 也信念自由&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我爱这少年讽刺吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这花开吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;粤语的魅力&#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;markdownIt-Anchor&#34; href=&#34;#粤语的魅力&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt; 粤语的魅力&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;​       相较于普通话而言，粤语在音调上有更多的抑扬顿挫。单从语言的角度来看，这样的一门语言会给人留下好听的印象，因此放入歌曲当中更有层次感受。内地人喜欢粤语歌，也是因为这一门语言具有独特的魅力，加上旋律之后会更加富有特色。即使不能够听懂歌词的含义，但是仍然会跟着哼唱也受到众多观众和乐迷的喜爱。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;​       粤语本身具有一种复古的味道。之所以会有复古的味道，是因为在发展的过程当中仍然保留了古汉语的元素。不少的语言为了适应时代的发展变得越来越简便，这个过程当中会省略或者放弃一些较为古老的词汇，让语言变得更加通俗易懂。但是在粤语当中仍然会有一些较为古老的词汇和发音，这就会这一门语言增加了历史的气息和文化的底蕴。由于古汉语元素的存在，也让这门语言有了更加古朴典雅的气息，放在粤语歌当中加上旋律和节奏就更加有味道。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Daily expressions&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你好&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你好&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你叫什么名字？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你叫咩啊？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;谢谢！&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;唔该！多谢嗮！&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;不好意思打扰你一下&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;唔好意思阻你一阵&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;在哪里呀？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;喺边度呀？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你在干什么？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你喺度做乜？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你吃饭了没？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;你食咗饭未？&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;​     我这样子讲你们应该还无法对粤语这门语言有自己的深刻感受。接下来，我会跟大家分享一首比较火的粤语歌，让我们在倾听中领略粤语中独特的美，为这次的演讲画上一个句号。在我看来，一场演讲只有得到观众的共鸣才能算的上成功，希望我的这次演讲能让你们从中获得一些东西。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;​     感谢你们的倾听。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img data-src=&#34;https://images.app.goo.gl/iPsMMpozEHeFgnnH7&#34; alt=&#34;https://images.app.goo.gl/iPsMMpozEHeFgnnH7&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[&lt;span class=&#34;exturl&#34; data-url=&#34;aHR0cHM6Ly95LnFxLmNvbS9uL3J5cXEvcGxheWVy&#34;&gt;https://y.qq.com/n/ryqq/player&lt;/span&gt;]:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jcool：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;有个女仔令我思想变得大个&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;当初&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我幼稚行为对你犯下大错&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;你话我唔识谂 用钱买无用饰品&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;你慢慢心淡觉得我对感情唔认真&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;要知道男人系天生嘅小朋友&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;小朋友弱点会忽略另一半感受&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;要改正好简单我只系欠调教&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;经历得多反而可以令到爱意浓厚&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vai：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;志明嘅世界永远好动带着可爱&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;佢冇时间迷茫 爱情错过却唔可再&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;从开始走到结尾哪个不会变大个&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但春娇想要那个你又有谁可以劝阻&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;等待 UFO 纵有变数&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最普通嘅佢哋世上遍布&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爱漫春天散落每个季节嘅消耗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;看着花瓣跌落过程撑得过衰老&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;欧阳：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;重新出发吗 huh 更渴望未来&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;以往这少年懂爱吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;仿佛不够&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;成长会进化吗 也信念自由&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我爱这少年讽刺吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这花开吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;留：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我爱你 你是唱将我做配合&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但你予我这过程细致给我培训&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;情与爱 太过复杂 我要太多喘息&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但你爱我嘅以后不会太过忐忑&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;当拥有嘅时候 又接近放手&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;循环播放剧情有多少个然后&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;如果系现实我会选择打破现实&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;喺你嘅世界里面我会选择慢慢渐入&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vai：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;志明嘅世界永远好动带着可爱&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;佢冇时间迷茫 爱情错过却唔可再&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;从开始走到结尾哪个不会变大个&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但春娇想要那个你又有谁可以劝阻&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;等待 UFO 纵有变数&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最普通嘅佢哋世上遍布&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爱漫春天散落每个季节嘅消耗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;看着花瓣跌落过程撑得过衰老&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;欧阳：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;重新出发吗 huh 更渴望未来&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;以往这少年懂爱吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;仿佛不够&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;成长会进化吗 也信念自由&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我爱这少年讽刺吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这花开吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Garyu：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;破碎婚姻里出身逼出佢嘅硬净&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;佢再牺牲佢嘅率真改变佢嘅硬颈&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;戴眼镜嘅佢明白波珠解决唔到逃避&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;要长大要负责任缩短两个人嘅距离&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;美梦里学会感嘅&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;你亦放肆你的爱&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;用力转载 越过比赛&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;为我掩盖 都因为爱&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;欧阳：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;重新出发吗 huh 更渴望未来&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;以往这少年懂爱吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;仿佛不够&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;成长会进化吗 也信念自由&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我爱这少年讽刺吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这花开吗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
